Does the project have
A risk of guarantee modification
Brother Chengze
What do we do now
This is a project meeting
Why did you bring him
He's my husband
All you talk about now is your husband
Afraid people will forget
Don't worry Mr Gu
Nobody will forget
After all you broke off the engagement in public
And I changed grooms in public
All of Nancheng knows
Heh
Miss Su
You submitted a guarantee withdrawal notice this morning
Today we need to clarify
The reasons and follow-up plans
Sure
Gu Group respects Miss Su's choice
Her sudden withdrawal is because of the wedding
Caused by personal feelings
My reason for withdrawing isn't personal feelings
It's because the supplementary agreement
Has these three problems
That's just your personal interpretation